Japanese Film Ephemera Collection
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Directors and films, Circa 1970-2014; Series I
  - 横井健司 = Yokoi Takeshi, 2006-2011 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - 横浜聡子 = Yokohama Satoko, 2006-2013 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - 横山一洋 = Yokoyama Kazuhiro, 2007-2011 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - 吉田喜重 = Yoshida Yoshishige = Yoshida Kijū, 1986-2008 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - 吉田恵輔 = Yoshida Keisuke, 2006-2013 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - 吉田健 = Yoshida Ken, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 26)
    Includes 高校教師 = Kōkō kyōshi
  - 吉田修一 = Yoshida Shūichi, 2007 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - 吉田大八 = Yoshida Daihachi, 2007-2010 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - 吉田康弘 = Yoshida Yasuhiro, 2006 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - 吉田裕亮 = Yoshida Yūsuke, 2006 (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - ラン ナイチョイ = Lan Naichoi, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 31)
    Includes 孔雀王 = Kujakuō = Kujakuoh
  - 李瑛 = Li Ying, 1999-2008 (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - 李相日 = Li Sang-il, 2006-2013 (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - 李闘士男 = Ri Toshio = Li Toshio, 2008-2010 (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - りんたろう = Rintarō, 2001 (Box 14, Folder 35)
    Includes メトロポリス = Metoroporisu = Metropolis
  - ジェリー ロンドン = Jerry London, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 36)
    Includes 将軍 = Shōgun = James Clavell's Shogun
  - 若木信吾 = Wakaki Shingo, 2007 (Box 14, Folder 37)
  - 若月治 = Wakatsuki Osamu, 1982 (Box 14, Folder 38)
  - 若月美刀 = Wakatsuki Bitō, 2006 (Box 14, Folder 39)
  - 若松孝二 = Wakamatsu Kōji, 1992-2008 (Box 14, Folder 40)
    Includes エロティックな関係 = Erotikku na kankei = Les liaisons erotiques
  - 若松節朗 = Wakamatsu Setsurō, 2000-2011 (Box 14, Folder 41)
    Includes ホワイトアウト = Howaito auto = Whiteout
  - 渡辺一志 = Watanabe Kazushi, 2007-2008 (Box 14, Folder 42)
  - 渡辺謙作 = Watanabe Kensaku, 2006-2008 (Box 14, Folder 43)
  - 渡邊孝好 = Watanabe Takayoshi, 1989-1997 (Box 14, Folder 44)
    Includes 君は僕をスキになる = Kimi wa boku o sukininaru; スキ! = Suki!; 香港大夜総会 タッチ＆マギー = Honkon daiyasōkai Tacchi & Magī = HongKong Daiyasokai Touch & Maggie
  - 渡辺寿 = Watanabe Hisashi, 2005 (Box 14, Folder 45)
  - 渡辺祐介 = Watanabe Yūsuke, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 46)
    Includes 刑事物語 くろしおの詩 893 = Keiji monogatari kuroshio no uta yakuza
  - 和田秀樹 = Wada Hideki, 2007-2012 (Box 14, Folder 47)
- Other film ephemera, 1975-2010; Series II
  The series is arranged in three sections: Films with multiple directors; Special film programs and festivals; and Film journals and newsletters. The films with multiple directors section is arranged by title of the film in the order of the Japanese syllabary. In cases where a single item includes multiple titles, those titles are separated by semicolons. Special film programs, festivals, and journals are arranged by the name of the sponsoring organization or theater or title.
  Series II consists of handbills, pamphlets, press kits, catalogs, and film newsletter documenting films directed by multiple directors, special film programs, and festivals.
  - Films with multiple directors
    Material is arranged by title of film.
    - 残照 = Zanshō, 1978 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - ウルトラマン物語 = Urutoraman monogatari, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - R246 Story = R246 Story, 2008 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - 三等高校生 = Santō kōkōsei, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - 映画なんです！ = Eiga nandesu!, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - 乱れからくり = Midare karakuri, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - 屋根裏の散歩者 = Yaneura no sanposha, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - マラニヤ = Maraniya, 2007 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - 帰ってきた若大将 = Kaettekita wakadaishō; 青春グラフィティ スニーカーぶるーす = Seishun gurafiti sunīkā burūsu, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - 歌謡曲だよ、人生は = Kayōkyoku dayo, jinsei wa, 2007 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - 学校の会談R = Gakkō no kaidan R, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Kiss! = Kiss!, 2009 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - 斬 Kill = Kiru Kill = Kill, 2008 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - ハローキティ 魔法の森のお姫さま = Harō Kiti mahō no mori no ohimesama, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - コワイ女 = Kowai onna, 2006 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - シャーリーの好色人生と転落人生 = Shārīno kōshoku jinsei to tenraku jinsei, 2008 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - 新訳 今昔物語 = Shinyaku Konjaku Monogatari, 2007 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - JM = JM, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - 妖女伝説セイレーン = Yōjo densetsu Seirēn, 2008 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - フリテンくん = Furiten kun, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - 若い人 = Wakai hito, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - 空の境界 = Sora no kyōkai, 2007-2008 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - 大脱出!脱出ゲーム The Movie = Daidasshutsu! Dasshutsu gēmu The Movie, 2009 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - ちびまる子ちゃん わたしの好きな歌 = Chibi Maruko chan watashi no sukina uta, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - 掌の小説 = Tenohira no shōsetsu = Palm of the hand stories, 2009 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Devotion - 小川紳介と生きた人々 = Devotion - Ogawa Shinsuke to ikita hotibito, 2002 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - 東京小説 = Tōkyō shōsetsu, 2006 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - おばあちゃんの思い出 = Obāchan no omoide, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - ドラミちゃん ミニドラSOS!!! = Dorami chan Minidora SOS!!!, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - ナイスの森 = Naisu no mori, 2004 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - 陽のあたる坂道 = Hi no ataru sakamichi, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - バカヤロー！２ ｢幸せになりたい。｣ = Bakayarō! 2 Shiawase ni naritai., 1989 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - ハッピィボーイズ = Happī bōizu = Happy Boys, 2009 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - パニック 4 Rooms = Panikku 4 rooms, 2009 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - 非女子図鑑 = Hijoshi zukan, 2008 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - フィルム メモワール = Firumu memowāru = FILM MÈMOIRE, 2006 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - ブルーフィルムズ = Burū firumuzu = Blue Films, 2003-2009 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - プラスワン = Purasu wan, 2006 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - 山谷 やられたらやりかえせ = Yama yararetara yarikaese, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - 夕映え少女 = Yūbae shōjo, 2008 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - 幽霊VS宇宙人 = Yūrei VS uchūjin, 2008 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - ユメ十夜 = Yume jūya, 2007 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - よみがえれカレーズ = Yomigaere Karēzu, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - ヨムトシヌ = Yomuto shinu = Death comic, 2009 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - ラブサイコ = Rabu saiko, 2006 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - 琉神マブヤー = Ryūjin Mabuyā = Ryujin Mabuyer, 2009 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Special film programs and festivals
    Material is arranged by name of sponsoring organization or theater.
    - アース・ビジョン 地球環境映像祭 = Āsu Bijon Chikyū Kankyō Eizōsai = Earth Vision Tokyo Global Environment Film Festival, 2009 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - あいち国際女性映画祭 = Aichi Kokusai Josei Eigasai = Aichi International Women's Film Festival, 2007 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - ACTミニシアター = Act Minishiatā, 2008 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - 浅草中映劇場 = Asakusa Chūei Gekijō, 2006 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - アップリンクファクトリー = Appurinku Fakutorī = Uplink Factory, 2008 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - 市川市文芸映画鑑賞会 = Ichikawa-shi Bubgei Eiga Kanshōkai, 2007 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - 一角座 = Ikkakuza, 2006 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - イメージフォーラム・フェスティバル = Imēji Fōramu Fesutibaru = Image Forum Festival, 1994-2008 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - イメージリングス背徳映画祭 = Imēji Ringusu Haitoku Eigasai, 2006 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - 上野オークラ劇場 = Ueno Ōkura Gekijō, 2008 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - 上野スタームービー = Ueno Sutā Mūbī, 2008 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - 映画美学校 = Eiga Bigakkō, 2007 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - 恵比寿ガーデンシネマ = Ebisu Gāden Shinema = Yebisu Garden Cinema, 2009 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - 大阪芸術大学 = Ōsaka Geijutsu Daigaku, 2006 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - 角川シネマ新宿 = Kadokawa Shinema Shinjuku, 2008 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - カナザワ映画祭 = Kanazawa Eigasai, 2009 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - 川崎市民ミュージアム = Kawasaki Shimin Myūjiamu = Kawasaki City Museum, 2006-2008 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - ガンダーラ映画祭 = Gandāra Eigasai, 2007 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - 吉祥寺バウスシアター = Kichijōji Bausu Shiatā = Kichijoji Baustheater, 2009 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - 紀伊國屋ホール = Kinokuniya Hōru = Kinokuniya Hall, 2008 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - 京都芸術劇場 = Kyōto Geijutsu Gekijō, 2008 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - 銀座シネパトス = Ginza Shinepatosu = Ginza Cine Pathos, 2009-2010 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - キネカ大森 = Kineka Ōmori, 2009 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - 京都シネマ = Kyōto Shinema = Kyoto Cinema, 2009 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - 錦之助映画祭り = Kinnosuke Eiga Matsuri, 2009 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - 神戸ドキュメンタリー映画祭 = Kobe Dokyumentarī Eigasai = Kobe Documentary Festival, 2009 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - 国立劇場 = Kunitachi Gekijō, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - 黒澤明記念ショートフィルムコンペティション = Kurosawa Akira Kinen Shōto Firumu Konpetishon = Akira Kurosawa Memorial Short Film Competition, 2004-2005 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - 江東区シネマプラザ = Kōtōku Shinema Puraza, 2008 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - 神戸映画資料館 = Kōbe Eiga Shiryōkan = Kobe Planet Film Archive, 2007-2008 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - 下北沢トリウッド = Shimokitazawa Toriuddo, 2008 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - シネカノン有楽町１丁目 = Shinekanon Yūrakuchō 1-chōme =, 2009 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - シネマート六本木 = Shinemāto Roppongi = Cinemart Roppongi, 2009 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - シネマアートン下北沢 = Shinema Āton Shimokitazawa = Cinema Artone Shimokitazawa, 2007-2008 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - シネマアンジェリカ = Shinema Anjerika = Cinema Angelica, 2006-2008 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - シネマヴェーラ渋谷 = Shinemavēra Shibuya = Cinemavera Shibuya, 2007-2009 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - シネマジャック＆ベティ = Shinema Jakku & Betī = Cinema Jack & Betty, 2009 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - シネマ秘宝館 = Shinema Hihōkan, 2009 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - 清水映画祭 = Shimizu Eigasai = Shimizu Film Festival, 2008 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - 下北沢 La Camera = Shimokitazawa Ra Kamera, 2009 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - 下高井戸シネマ = Shimotakaido Shinema, 2009 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - JAPAN国際コンテンツフェスティバル = Japan kokusai kontentsu fesutibaru = Japan International Contents Festival = CoFesta, 2009 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - 城西国際大学 = Jōsai Kokusai Daigaku = Josa International University, 2005-2008 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - 新文芸坐 = Shin Bungeiza, 2007-2008 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - 神保町シアター = Jinbō-chō Shiatā = Jinbocho Theater, 2008-2009 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - SKIPシティ国際Dシネマ映画祭 = Skip Shiti Kokusai D-Shinema Eigasai = SKIP City International D-Cinema Festival, 2008 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - 世田谷フィルムフェスティバル = Setagaya Firumu Fesutibaru = Setagaya Film Festival, 2009 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - 仙台短篇映画祭 = Sendai Tanpen Eigasai = Sendai Shortfilm Festival, 2009 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - ゼロ年代映画祭 = Zero-nendai Eigasai, 2009 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - 調布映画祭ショートフィルムコンペティション = Chōfu Eigasai Shōto Firumu Konpetishon = Chofu Short Film/ Video Competition, 2006-2007 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - テアトル新宿 = Teatoru Shinjuku, 2008 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - 天神シネクラブ = Tenjin Shinekurabu, 2006 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Dejima Japanese Film Festival = Dejima Japanese Film Festival, 2006 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - 東京芸術大学 = Tōkyō Geijutsu Daigaku = Tokyo University of Arts = Tokyo National University of Fine Arts and Music, 2007 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - 東京国際映画祭 = Tōkyō Kokusai Eigasai = Tokyo International Film Festival, 1998-2002 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - 東京国際レズビアン＆ゲイ映画祭 = Tōkyō Kokusai Rezubian & Gei Eigasai = Tokyo International Lesbian & Gay Film & Video Festival, 1996-2008 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - 東京国際ファンタスティック映画祭 = Tōkyō Kokusai Fantasutikku Eigasai = Tokyo International Fantastic Film Festival, 1992-1994 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - ゆうばり国際冒険・ファンタスティック映画祭 = Yūbari Kokusai Bōken Fantasutikku Eigasai = Yubari International Fantastic Adventure Film Festival, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - 東京国立近代美術館フィルムセンター = Tōkyō Kokuritsu Kindai Bijutsukan Firumu Sentā = National Film Center, The National Museum of Modern Art, Tokyo, 2005-2009 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - 東京都現代美術館 = Tōkyōto Gendai Bijutsukan = Museum of Contemporary Art Tokyo, 2006 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - 東京日仏学院 = Tōkyō Nichifutsu Gakuin = L'Institut Franco-Japonais de Tokyo, 2007 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - トーキョー・フィルム・メーカーズ・コンベンション = Tōkyō Firumu Mēkāzu Konbenshon = Tokyo Film Makers Convention, 2002 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - 東劇 = Tōgeki = Togeki, 2009 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - 十日町シネマパラダイス = Tōkamachi Shinema Paradaisu = Tokachimachi Cinema Paradise, 2009 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - 所沢市民文化センターミューズマーキーホール = Tokorozawa Shimin Bunka Sentā Mūzu Mākī Hōru, 2008 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - ドキュメンタリー・ドリーム・ショー 山形in東京 = Dokyumentarī Dorīmu Shō Yamagata in Tōkyō = Documentary Dream Show Yamagata in Tokyo, 2006 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - なかのZERO視聴覚ホール = Nakano Zero Shichōkaku Hōru, 2008 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - 長岡アジア映画祭 = Nagaoka Ajia Eigasai = Nagaoka Asian Film Festival, 2009 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - 日本映画専門チャンネルHD = Nihon Eiga Senmon Channeru HD, 2008 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Neoneo坐 = Neoneoza, 2007-2008 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - ニューシネマフェスティバル = Nyū Shinema Fesutibaru = New Cinema Festival, 2009 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - はいさいFFESTA = Haisai Festa, 2008 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - 爆音映画祭 = Bakuon Eigasai = Bakuon Film Festival, 2008 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - ビジュアルアーツ専門学校大阪 = Bijuaru Ātsu Senmon Gakkō Ōsaka = Visual Arts College Osaka, 2009 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - ぴあフィルムフェスティバル = Pia Firumu Fesutibaru = Pia Film Festival, 2007-2008 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - ファンタスティックシアター = Fantasutikku Shiatā = Fantastic Theater, 2006 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - ブリリアショートショートセンター = Buriria Shōto Shōto Sentā = Brillia ShortsShorts Center, 2009 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Frictional Movie Fes. = Frictional Movie Fes., 1989 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Berlin International Film Festival New Cinema from Japan = Berlin International Film Festival New Cinema from Japan, 1999-2001 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - ポレポレ東中野 = Porepore Higashinakano = Theatre Pole-Pole Higashi-Nakano, 2008 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - 水戸短編映像祭セレクション = Mito Tanpen Eizōsai Selekushon = Mito Short Film Festival Selection, 2007 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - 山形国際ドキュメンタリー映画際 = Yamagata Kokusai Dokyumentarī Eigasai = Yamagata International Documentary Film Festival, 2008-2009 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - 山口情報芸術センター = Yamaguchi Jōhō Geijutsu Sentā = Yamaguchi Center for Arts and Media = YCAM, 2009 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - ユーロスペース = Yūro Supēsu = Euro Space, 2007-2008 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - 横濱学生映画祭 = Yokohama Gakusei Eigasai, 2007 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - 横浜黄金町映画祭 = Yokohama Koganechō Eigasai, 2008 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - 横浜市大倉山記念館 = Yokohama-shi Ōkurayama Kinenkan, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - ラピュタ阿佐ヶ谷 = Rapyuta Asagaya = Laputa Asagaya, 2006-2008 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - 早稲田松竹 = Waseda Shōchiku, 2008 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - 早稲田大学 = Waseda Daigaku = Waseda University, 2009 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Film journals and newsletters
    Material is arranged by title of the publication.
    - アップリンクインフォメーション = Appurinku Infomēshon = Uplink Information, 2008 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - 兄貴 = Aniki, 2008 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - アムキー = Amky = AmK.Y., 2009 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - アルテリオ・シネマニュース = Aruterio Shinema Nyūsu = Cinema News, 2008-2009 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Independent: Pia Film Festival Official News Paper, 1993-1994 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - 映画美術スタッフ塾 = Eiga Bijustsu Sutaffujuku, 2007 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - 映画の國 = Eiga no Kuni, 2009 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - MCAC ニュース = Mcac Nyūsu = Mcac News, 2006-2007 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - キネマ旬報 = Kinema Junpō, 2009-2010 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - キョーバシ・モード = Kyōbashi Mōdo = Kyobashi Mode, 2008 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Sakurazaka FunC, 2009 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - シネマ・アベニュー = Shinema Abenyū = Cinema Avenue, 2009 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - シネマ歌舞伎 = Shinema Kabuki, 2007 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Cinema Square Magazine, 1985 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - シネマバフ = Shinema Bafu = Cinema Buff, 2007 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - シネマ夢倶楽部 = Shinema Yume Kurabu, 2008 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - シネ砦 = Shine Toride = Fort Cinema, 2006 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - ステナイデラブ・シネマ = Sutenaide Rabu Shinema = Sutenaide Love Cinema, 2009 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - チャンバラ = 血矢夢馬羅 = Chanbara, 2008 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - TIFF Times = 東京国際映画祭 = Tōkyō Kokusai Eigasai = Tokyo International Film Festival, 2009 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - 日本映画学校 = Nihon Eiga Gakkō = Japan Academy of Moving Images, 2009 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - ニューシネマ・ジャパン = New Cinema from Japan, 2009 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - 東映キネマ旬報 = Tōei Kinema Junpō, 2009 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - 東スポシネマ = Tōsupo Shinema = Tokyo Sports Cinema, 2008 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Filmnetwork = Film Network, 2009 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Film List Toei Animation 1956-, Circa 2009 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - 名画座通信 = Meigaza Tsūshin, 2009 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Boid Paper, 2007 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Vox 46, 2009 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - シネマ・シティ：横浜と映画 = Shinema Shiti Yokohama to eiga, 2005 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - ムッシュ・シネマ = Musshu Shinema = Monsieur Cinéma, 2009 (Box 16, Folder 10)